diyseo.com 2011-12-31

# SEO Software for Your Small Business | DIYSEO

## Privacy Policy

This is the web site of DIYSEO LLC, a provider of [SEO Software](http://www.diyseo.com/)

Our postal address is:

1333 N. Kingsbury St., Suite 204  
Chicago, IL, 60642

We can be reached via e-mail at [info@diyseo.com](mailto:info@diyseo.com) or you can reach us via the [see contact page](http://www.diyseo.com/company/contact).

This Privacy Policy describes the information DIYSEO, LLC ("DIYSEO") may collect about you through your use of the DIYSEO search engine optimization service and related web sites (collectively, the "DIYSEO Site"). It also describes how DIYSEO uses your information, how DIYSEO protects it, and what choices you have on how that information is used.

### Information Collection and Use by DIYSEO

DIYSEO collects and uses information voluntarily submitted by a user, such as a user's name, email address, URLs, keywords, and credit card payment information, in connection with the services provided by DIYSEO on behalf of such user. DIYSEO may also share such information with its affiliated companies and business partners (such as agents or subcontractors) who are acting on DIYSEO's behalf to support your customer relationship with DIYSEO, unless otherwise agreed by you or required by law.

DIYSEO may also log non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the DIYSEO Site. This data is used to manage the DIYSEO Site, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to visitors. User IP addresses may also be recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

DIYSEO may also use a user's email address to send updates, such as a newsletter or news regarding DIYSEO's products and services. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by clicking an "opt out" link located at the bottom of the update.

Unless otherwise agreed by you or required by law, information collected by DIYSEO may be (i) used by DIYSEO for marketing and business purposes, (ii) retained by DIYSEO indefinitely, and (iii) sold or otherwise transmitted to third parties.

### Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Systems

DIYSEO may use cookies or other similar tracking means to store user's preferences and to record session information. DIYSEO may link the information it stores in its tracking systems to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the DIYSEO Site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some tracking systems, or notify you when a tracking systems is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your tracking system preferences -- however, you may have to enable tracking systems from DIYSEO in order to use some functions on the DIYSEO Site.

### Links

The DIYSEO Site may contain links to other sites. DIYSEO is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the DIYSEO Site.

### Sharing and Disclosure of Information DIYSEO Collects

In addition to the disclosures otherwise described in this privacy statement, DIYSEO may disclose personal information to a third party if DIYSEO believes that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by DIYSEO, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the DIYSEO Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of DIYSEO's products and services. DIYSEO reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of DIYSEO or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time DIYSEO may make changes to its privacy policy. If DIYSEO makes changes, it will post them on the DIYSEO Site so users will be aware of what information DIYSEO collects, how DIYSEO uses it, and when DIYSEO may disclose it. A user is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, DIYSEO is going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection it will notify you by posting a notice on the DIYSEO Site for 30 days.

### Contacting DIYSEO

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the DIYSEO Site, or your dealings with the DIYSEO Site, please contact us at: [info@diyseo.com](mailto:info@diyseo.com).

Want to learn more about the DIYSEO solution? Start your [Free Trial](https://www.diyseo.com/signup) today!

Wondering how well your website is doing with SEO? Get a Free SEO Report!
